Yode Wang

UX Designer / Front-end developer

✓ yode0419@gmail.com.tw



// https://yode0419.github.io/portfolio



Profile

I am a challenger in the field of UX design and front-end development, with a background in civil structural engineering. Despite the different fields, I possess core capabilities required in these areas: communication, coordination, design thinking, and problem-solving. Drawing, 3D modeling, presenting ideas, and considering feasibility are my specialties.

During my journey of self-study for this career transition, I have completed the Google UX Design course, accumulated UX portfolio projects, and built up my personal website. I am excited to bring my passion to UX, web and product design, aiming to provide users with enhanced experiences.

Experiences

2023.06 - 2023.08 Google UX Design Professional Certificate

Learning UX / Portfolio / Web Development

2016.09 - 2023.06 **Structural Engineer**

TYLIN Construction Consultant Structural Design / Bridge Design / Project Management

- · Taoyuan Metro Green Line
- · Kaohsiung Metro Red Line
- · Taoyuan Airport Terminal 3
- · Hualien-Taitung Railway Dual-Track Project

2019.13 - 2020.12 Working Holiday in Australia

Perth / Melbourne

- · Crazy Sales Warehouse
- · The Pamphleteers Mail Delivery
- · Treviso Farm Grape Worker

Education

2013.09 - 2015.09 National Taiwan University

Master's Degree in Civil Engineering, Structural Division

2009.09 - 2013.09 National Taiwan University

AutoCAD

Bachelor's Degree in Civil Engineering

Skills

Graphic Design	3D Modeling	Front-End	Office	Languages
Figma	Blender	Development	Word	English
Photoshop	SketchUp	HTML	PowerPoint	(Intermediate Level)
Illustrator	F	CSS	Excel	French
Procreate	Engineering Drawing	JavaScript	VBA	(Beginner Level)
		Bootstrap		